{
    "quiz": {
        "ObjectiveC": [
                   {"question":"What is Xcode ? give the brief desciption of the xcode & How it works on the mac?give the brief desciption of the xcode & How it works on the mac? What is Xcode ? give the brief desciption of the xcode & How it works on the mac?give the brief desciption of the xcode & How it works on the mac? ", "answer":"Xcode is an IDE, which is used to develope iOS Application, and it has the many controls for managing the perfect view of the screen & user satisfaction is necessary for the similar purpose   For the development it use the xcode & simulatoe  For the development it use the xcode & simulatoe for thanks for contactio9nfg uds nbvszbh++"},
                   {"question":"What is Xcode ? give the brief desciption of the component", "answer":"For the development it use the xcode & simulatoe forb bsbds ysd  sdkbs hbkmmhjsvk  hjbskdf bjk jkbnsvds hvnmsnbdfs thanks for contactio9nfg uds nbvszbh  For the development it use the xcode & simulatoe forb bsbds ysd  sdkbs hbkmmhjsvk  hjbskdf bjk jkbnsvds hvnmsnbdfs thanks for contactio9nfg uds nbvszbhFor the development it use the xcode & simulatoe forb bsbds ysd  sdkbs hbkmmhjsvk  hjbskdf bjk jkbnsvds hvnmsnbdfs thanks for contac"},
                   {"question":"What is Core Data",  "answer":"s hvnmsnbdfs thanks for contactio9nfg uds nbvszbh  For the development it use the xcode & simulatoe forb bsbds ysd  sdkbs hbkmmhjsvk  hjbskdf bjk jkbnsvds hvnmsnbdfs thanks for contactio9nfg uds nbvszbhFor the development it use the xcode & simulatoe forb bsbds ysd  sdkbs hbkmmhjsvk  hjbskdf bjk jkbnsvd"},
                   {"question":"What is Delegates and Data sources?",  "answer":"hvnmsnbdfs thanks for contactio9nfg uds nbvszbh  For the development it use the xcode & simulatoe forb bsbds ysd  sdkbs hbkmmhjsvk  hjbskdf bjk jkbnsvds hvnmsnbdfs thanks for c"},
                   {"question":"What is new in iOS7?",  "answer":"iOS Application, and it has the many controls for managing the perfect view of the screen & user satisfaction is necessary for the similar purpose   For the development it use the xcode & simulatoe forb bsbds ysd  sdkbs hbkmmhjsvk  hjbskdf bjk jkbnsvds hvnmsnbdfs thanks for contactio9nfg uds nbvszbh  For the development it use the xcode & simulatoe forb bsbds ysd  sdkbs hbkmmhjsvk  hjbskdf bjk jkbnsvds hvnmsnbdfs thanks for contactio9nfg ud"},
                   {"question":"What is the latest version of iOS?",  "answer":"iOS has manay versions, which compromise the ffsdfsd"},
                    
                       {"question":"What is the Sqlite?",  "answer":"Many controls for managing the perfect view of the screen & user satisfaction is necessary for the similar purpose   For the developm"},
                       {"question":"What is Mac OS?",  "answer":"It has the many controls for managing the perfect view of the screen & user satisfaction is necessary for the similar purpose   For the developm"},
                       {"question":"What is Super View?",  "answer":"Super View  has the many controls for managing the perfect view of the screen & user satisfaction is necessary for the similar purpose   For the developm"},
                       {"question":"What is the View controller ?",  "answer":"View COntroller it has the many controls for managing the perfect view of the screen & user satisfaction is necessary for the similar purpose   For the developm"}
                       
                   ]
        
    }
}
